Start digging there !
He has the key in his eye .
If you 're afraid , go home . I 'll finish up .
So many assholes in my life !
You didn 't answer !
I never answer while driving .
You 've become so damn civilized .
That 's more like it !
- Where 's Walid ? - How would I know ?
I understand your concerns .
I 've been through it myself .
You 'll manage . Don 't panic , all right ?
You 'll have time to ...
Hello , sir .
Not on time once this year !
It 's you who comes early !
You 'll have time to catch up .
- Nice hair ! - Fuck off !
Behave !
The project will be a filmed investigative report .
You 're free to choose the subject and length .
What I care about most is the deadline .
You have 15 days to do it .
Not a day more .
Hear that , Walid ?
Loud and clear .
I also want a detailed paper outlining the shoot .
Work alone or in teams .
Up W ! you .
We 'll set a date with the jury
once I 've validated the projects .
What I want above all
are extremely exclusive stories .
I want nothing banal .
And please , nothing on the Revolution !
I have nothing against it ,
but last year I had 20 projects
on this desk , all of them identical .
So ...
Exclusive stories only , Walid .
Got it ? Exclusive stories .
Show us what you 've got .
Count on me .
Good luck .
God have mercy on him .
Bless you .
- Thanks for helping . - It was nothing .
Here ...
No , no , son . I can 't ...
Thank you .
For the old man , if you want .
We 'll pray for him in the cemetery .
God have mercy on him .
Yasmine ...
Yes , Grandpa . Where have you been ?
No , I called .
I answered your missed call . You didn 't pick up .
Anyway ...
Don 't wait for me for lunch .
Where are you going ?
All right .
Heat something up when you get back .
Make sure you eat .
Take your pills . And no snacks .
Drop off the truck when you 're done .
I will , don 't worry .
Relax .
I 'm in class , Grandpa . Bye ...
I 'll call you later .
You just blew him off !
- He is such a pain ! - He worries .
I 'm not 5 , Bilel .
He worries anyway .
And least you know your grandpa .
At least you know your parents !
What the fuck ?
Sorry , I didn 't mean it .
- Same dumb-ass . - Butt out .
That tastes weird .
- What ? - Is it tuna ?
It tastes like tuna ?
Chicken ?
Piranha !
I have an idea .
A story on suckers .
With Walid as an example .
Good idea !
You 're both suckers .
Why not prostitution ?
We 'll interview Bilel 's family for details .
Why my family ?
Enough , 9W5 -
Your joking around always leads to fights .
This time I 'm serious .
I heard a weird story . I 'm usually skeptical .
Another dumb story ?
Let him talk .
Can I tell him to fuck himself ?
Be my guest .
My mom 's friend came over yesterday .
Her daughter 's a nurse in a psychiatric hospital .
She said a patient there
bit a nurse who was trying to treat her .
Almost took her nose off .
Lots of blood .
I asked my mom . She heard about this patient years ago .
There were articles about her .
They called her " Mongia " .
I asked my mom to tell me more .
She was found 20 years ago on a highway ,
naked and mutilated .
Her throat slashed open .
Without any ID on her .
Tunisian ? Tourist ?
The police rushed her to hospital .
They stitched her up .
After she woke up from anesthesia ,
she became aggressive .
She started screaming .
Spoke in weird voices . Crazy !
No one ever went there asking about her .
- Good subject ? - Where 's the investigation ?
And the exclusivity ?
A crazy lady is nothing .
- Not so simple ! - As for exclusivity ,
we 'll be the first to film her .
They won 't let us .
Filming in an asylum isn 't easy !
My contact will let us film .
It 's more than that .
We need a permit . Or else when we finish ,
they 'll refuse the story for being unethical .
I 'll get a permit .
The subject is a madwoman ?
It 's everything told about her .
- That she 's a witch . - Like your mom .
Like your sister ! I 'm being serious !
Why a witch ?
She scares them all .
She crawls around speaking in strange voices .
What crap !
Sometimes her room is empty and she appears from nowhere .
Weird stuff .
She 's just crazy .
I don 't believe in that stuff .
It may be a good subject . It 's about work , not beliefs .
When ?
- Tuesday . - Why not tomorrow ?
Why the rush ?
Tomorrow 's good .
Yasmine !
Your camera , my recorder .
She 'll see to the rest .
I don 't buy it , but it 's all we got .
- You 're in ? - Yep .
That 's it .
Here I am . Don 't worry ,
God protect you .
What 's wrong ?
I saw her again .
I saw her again , Grandpa .
Don 't panic .
Ask God to protect you .
Recite the verses I taught you .
I 'm here now , my child .
I 'm here , my child .
I 'm here .
Grandpa ...
please forgive me .
I know it 's hard for you . Forgive me .
Don 't worry about me .
Grandpa ...
Forgive me , Grandpa .
Forgive me .
What ?
Where are you ?
I 'm coming .
I 'm on my way .
Faster !
Move it , shithead !
Out of the way !
You called your contact at the asylum ?
I 'm talking to you !
What , Bilel ?
You told her we 're coming to film ?
Yes , must I repeat it 20 times ?
I called her , I swear .
Just to make sure .
I really did .
We 'll interview the director of the asylum .
No problem . I 'd planned on it anyway .
He 's a bit of a dick .
Like you .
You 're sure we can film Mongia in the asylum ?
Yes , don 't worry .
We 'll see .
I bet he 's lying .
Walid , here we go again . I 'm not doing this for nothing !
Don 't start blaming everything on me .
The idiot next to you is talking out his ass .
- I know you . - No , you don 't .
We 're used to your immaturity !
- I did everything . - Enough !
Bullshit !
My contact is calling .
Shut up , asshole .
We 're on the way , Baya .
Yasmine , what 's wrong ?
Nothing .
You both ignore me !
What 's your problem ? What do you want ?
WhY are you upset ?
I didn 't sleep well .
Shut up !
Fucking shit !
Why are you angry ? What is it , honey ?
Stop kissing me , shithead !
I 'll put my music on .
Whatever the fuck you want .
- Speak , sir . - Is that okay ?
It 's fine .
Baya , do I look okay ?
Camera ... and rolling .
Ready ?
Let 's go .
Welcome , Doctor .
First , we 'd all like to thank you
for having us today . You must be busy .
Can you introduce yourself to us ?
I 'm Dr. Fakhri lmed ,
psychiatrist ,
I studied in Paris
and was an intern in Tunisia and abroad .
As my colleagues know ,
I 'm the youngest director of this facility .
We 're changing things . Like this ward .
We now treat patients
we couldn 't take on in the past .
I was lucky , when I was young ,
to train with great psychiatrists .
I hope to show what they taught me ,
but that 's for others to say .
Enough about me .
Thank you .
We came to discuss one patient
among the 40 you mentioned . Her name is Mongia .
Tell us about her .
We have no patient who goes by that name .
Do we have a Mong ... ?
Just to remind you , it 's Mongia
who attacked one of the nurses here .
That never happened . I 'd have been informed .
You obviously weren 't .
We only have 40 patients . None of them attacked a nurse .
It 's untrue .
It 's a well-known case .
Mongia is not her real name .
She was found 20 years ago
on a highway with her throat cut .
She supposedly uses ...
I don 't know who you 're talking about .
Check the patient registry . You won 't find her .
So in fact you don 't know all your patients ?
She 's not in this hospital .
Can we move on or do you have more questions ?
To refresh your memory , Mongia is well known ...
My memory is fresh .
She is not our patient .
Tell us if we 're wrong .
A lot of people talk about the incident .
People talk ...
We have a great success rate with our clinical cases .
One of the patients here isn 't considered a witch ?
A witch ?
Witchcraft is part of various cultures and religions .
Even in the Koran .
We believe in science ,
but you 're babbling about sorcery and witches .
End of interview .
It 's just one case .
Baya , have them pack up
and leave .
Can we film here ?
Don 't film anything !
Just leave , please .
Okay , enough .
I 'll take the mic .
Remove it .
Good job , Walid .
Let 's go .
Why didn 't you warn him ?
I couldn 't bring it up .
You should have told me before .
I thought it was okay .
I looked so dumb .
I need my job . Your project can 't fuck it up .
You should have told me .
I couldn 't know .
What now ?
Bribe the guards so you can film the patient .
- Are you sure ? - Of course .
- Money will do it . - Sure !
Just a second .
I told you he was useless .
Now , let 's see .
$ 0 ?
They 'll need something .
Something ?
Money , dickwad ! Not peanuts .
I have nothing !
I know . You 're always broke !
Our 40 dinars for gas . Take it .
20 from each of us . Pay the rest .
- How cute ! - Just go !
We 're good . Here 's 40 dinars .
He didn 't put in any money .
Not one cent .
So stingy !
We made a deal . Wait until I call you .
- I 'll call . - No , I 'll call .
It must be today .
Stop it or you can keep your money .
I 'll call you .
See you later .
All good ?
Yes , but it 'll be a night shoot .
Why ?
Because we only paid 40 dinars .
We saw you .
I did everything . My hair is soaking .
No more excuses .
I did all the back and forth !
Are you okay ?
Yasmine ! Are you all right ?
We 're waiting for you .
Come on .
Monia works nights .
Nice to meet you .
Don 't make a sound .
I 'm taking a huge risk .
Baya , we 're good .
It 's the guards .
Okay , but we 're good .
What 's your name ?
Bilel .
Like the soccer player . Great name !
You like soccer ?
No , badminton .
Don 't like soccer ?
Love is in the air .
She 'll teach you soccer .
Soccer for the sucker .
Dangerous patients are kept here .
The director was unsettled
when you mentioned her .
Mongia 's been here over 20 years .
God protect us .
Why do you say that ?
Everybody is scared of Mongia .
Why call her a witch ?
You 'll soon see .
Witch or not , all we want is to film her .
Witchcraft is such a load of crap .
So she can 't fly ?
When she first came here ,
she fasted for months and lost no weight .
No kidding .
She bit the ear off a male nurse .
They once found her , throat cut , limbs in chains .
They stitched her up and she tore it open .
Witch or not ?
Did he scare you ?
Foufou is harmless .
Are you okay ?
I want no trouble .
Do your stuff fast .
Don 't worry .
Who 's going in ?
Me , the camera , Bilel ...
Not me . Use the camera mic .
Scared ?
Not at all .
Mongia , you have guests .
Follow me .
Listen to me . Film from here .
No closer . Sit here .
Okay .
I 'll do my rounds and come back .
I 'll leave Monia here .
Be careful , please !
Why do you care about Mongia ?
Can you keep quiet ?
You have Facebook ?
Yes .
Hello ...
I 'm Yasmine . This is Bilel .
We came to film you .
Don 't bother ! She won 't talk !
What happened before they brought you here ?
Don 't get close .
Yasmine .
This is a map .
The area you were found in .
Do you recall the exact location ?
It 's you ...
M0ngia !
Run !
Monia , call the guards !
Yasmine , run !
Run !
A cat made these scratches ?
Yes , an alley cat .
So you all accompanied her ?
Why are you so worried ?
I 'm not , Uncle Bashir .
When she tried to feed the cat ...
I lied to you , Grandpa .
Walid 's cat did it . That 's why he 's upset .
It was my puss ) ! -
I mean my mom 's cat .
Her cat .
A cat ...
We have to go .
I 'll drive you .
It 's fine .
Let me , guys .
- We 'll go eat . - Night , Uncle Bashir .
Goodnight .
Thanks , guys !
Wait , Bilel .
Here 's the map .
Thanks .
Goodnight .
I may be old , but I 'm not na 'l 've .
- What 's wrong ? - You can talk to me .
Why lie ?
I 'm not lying . Walid 's cat scratched me .
Listen ...
I 'm responsible for you .
Your mom asked me to look after you .
I promised her I would .
Don 't give me reason to worry , please .
All right , I promise .
Don 't worry .
Give me a kiss .
Get going -
Let me kiss you .
Stop , you 'll break my jaw .
Listen !
What ?
See the sheikh again .
It 's been ages .
I don 't want to see him again .
You still dream about the woman in black ?
Yes .
I saw the sheikh and still dream of her .
Why see him again ?
Do it for me .
I don 't like him ...
- Please , for me . - Okay .
This is the last time !
- Okay . - The last time , I swear .
All right .
Make us two sandwiches .
Sausage ?
- 2 or 3 sausages ? - Just 2 .
One with 3 , one with 2 .
Coming up .
What a fucking night !
- What did you do with Moma ' ? - Monk ?
The soccer fan !
What are you talking about ?
No salad for me .
Give me an egg , please .
Yes , Yasmine .
Are you sure ?
It 's no joke . Tomorrow we 'll go shoot .
You 're fucking crazy .
Don 't forget your equipment .
And tell Walid
not to forget his .
I 'll tell him .
Meet at the university .
Don 't be late .
All right .
See you tomorrow .
See you .
She wants to finish what we started .
What 's wrong ?
Look me in the eyes .
She has bigger balls than you .
That hurt !
Master ,
she wouldn 't come .
I tried , but in vain .
No problem .
My child ,
you 've grown .
She looks like her mother .
Thank you .
What 's wrong ?
Tell him .
Tell him nothing 's wrong .
Perfect .
It 's not true .
Every night I watch over her .
She sleeps poorly
and still sees the woman in black .
What do you see ?
Answer the sheikh .
I heard him , Grandpa .
What do you see ?
You know what I see .
Must I repeat it ?
You recited the verses ?
Yes , and it doesn 't help .
I 'll be late for school .
Excuse me . Yasmine !
I 'm sorry .
You didn 't tell her ?
I couldn 't .
I promised her mother .
I 'm scared for her .
God have mercy .
Amen .
No , Walid .
I get sick behind .
- I won 't switch . - Bilel , get in .
Such a fucking pain !
Hurts from behind ?
What a dirty mind ! Stop it .
Bilel , just get in .
Don 't piss me off in the morning .
Get in and stop arguing !
Come on , baby . Sit on my lap .
Stop it , asshole .
Take the next right .
Why a road map ? Use Google !
No network .
- What 's wrong ? - I feel sick .
- Gonna puke . - God !
- Pull over . - Don 't puke in Bashir 's car .
- Open the door ! - Use the other side .
Don 't die , asshole .
Run !
- Just like a pregnant woman . - Help him !
Wash your face in the puddle .
Get the fuck away .
- Need your gynecologist ? - Asshole !
- What 's her number ? - You okay ?
How far along are you ?
Walid , go see what he wants .
Hey there .
Good morning . You okay ?
Our friend is a little sick , that 's all .
I have water .
We have water too .
Where are you heading ?
Nearby . Not far ...
Where ?
Not too far from here .
Hello , sir .
Good morning , miss .
If you need anything , ask . Don 't be shy .
Thanks , we 're fine .
- It 's up to you . - We 're really fine .
God be with you .
Get better , bro .
Peace on you .
All better , Bilel ?
Come on , man .
How are you feeling ?
- Tell me , sweetheart . - Get in .
- Are you in pain ? - Shut up !
Get in . Stop nagging -
The first pregnancy is tough . Next one will be easier .
Why didn 't you use protection ?
Peace on you .
This guy is a real stalker . How creepy .
You Okay ?
Fine .
Still no network ?
Nothing .
Pull over . Let 's ask him .
Think so ?
He must know the area .
- Come with me . - Okay .
Hi , sir .
We wanted to ask ...
Deaf ...
There 's a village here .
Where is it ?
A woman was found here long ago .
Where was she from ?
How helpful .
Why is he shouting ?
Yes , Walid ?
That 's the spot .
You sure ?
I am .
Yasmine !
Yes ?
Bilel , let 's check this way .
Why ?
It 's a path .
Let 's climb up , not down .
He can sense paths .
It really feels like a path .
Yes , it does . Come and follow us .
Come on , Walid .
Hurry , shithead .
How do you feel now ? At home with the animals ?
In the Name of Allah , protector against harm
in Heaven , on Earth , All-Knowing ...
Take the tripod .
Give it to me .
Hand it to me .
Wait ! Come on ...
Fuck ! It 's wet !
We 're stranded . Sure it 's here ?
- Yes . - We can 't go back .
Don 't be a pussy .
- Give me the camera . - Wait .
Give it to me in one piece .
I 'm very tired .
We should go back . Know where we 're going ?
We 're following Walid .
Let 's go back .
Don 't be wimps . It 's just a walk in the forest .
You know how to get back ?
Why would we go back ?
You 'll get us lost .
We must almost be there .
Almost ? You know where we are ?
Come on , Walid .
We 're almost there .
What the hell ? We 're going around in circles !
I can 't walk anymore .
Stop complaining . Try to enjoy .
Enjoy what ? Shut up and enjoy the silence .
What ?
What 's she eating ?
Yasmine , wait .
Stop , Yasmine !
What the fuck is that ?
Take the stuff .
Wait , don 't be afraid !
Don 't be afraid !
Welcome .
I didn 't know you were coming .
I could have driven you here .
We didn 't know the village name .
- Feeling better , bro ? - Fine .
Careful next time you drink .
Sorry .
I 'm Saber , at your service .
Nice to meet you . Yasmine , Walid , Bilel .
Welcome .
Come have something to drink .
Come on .
A nice hot tea .
Go make the tea .
Nice place here , Saber .
Welcome .
Thanks .
I searched this spot on Google .
I didn 't find it .
What ?
We couldn 't find it on the map .
Qkay ...
So why are you here ?
We 're journalism students .
Great !
Last year .
We heard rumors .
Over 20 years ago ,
by the road near the forest ,
they found a mutilated woman .
The state police found her .
Algia ? The crazy woman ?
No , Mongia .
It 's an old story . I know nothing about it .
Can we find someone who remembers ?
There are no witnesses left .
The women here don 't talk to strangers .
You really love meat .
For sure .
Meat is good .
I bet .
Very good tea , Saber .
Shall we go ?
Where to ?
- Stay for dinner . - No thanks .
No , you have to . I brought some fresh meat .
I asked the women to cook .
We really must be going .
We should stay .
- Night is falling . - It 's nice here .
What about the forest ?
- How do we get home ? - We eat fast .
And what about Bashir ?
- Text him . - With no network ?
What 's wrong ?
No network .
Yes , up on the roof .
Call from there .
Thanks , Saber .
You 're welcome .
And what will you cook for us ?
Meat .
Yasmine .
" Mongia attacked a nurse . "
" The nurses consider her a witch ... "
Answer .
Please answer .
Answer , my child .
They drink lots of wine .
- No signal . - Stop .
$ 0 ?
Nothing .
It 's fucking freezing !
You won 't get a signal !
I have one bar ...
Grandpa ,
don 't worry about me .
I 'm studying with the guys .
Shit !
Stop it ! Stop it right now !
- What is it ? - Stop making noise !
Look at this .
Dumb ass !
God have mercy on us .
Good tongue .
Where 's the meat ?
Here it comes .
Thank you .
Is this the hotel you asked about ?
I hope you like it .
Why aren 't you eating ?
It 's delicious .
Come on , eat .
Eat up !
Your daughter ?
She 's your daughter ?
Who , Rebeh ?
My niece . Her dad died .
We saw her in the woods .
- Did she bother you ? - No ...
My late brother
married his cousin . You know the risk .
She 's a bit special .
But she 's harmless !
God protect her !
- Eat now . - Thanks .
How can you leave now ? It 's dark out !
Walid can drive .
Yasmine has bad night vision .
Where is Walid ?
You drive , like we said .
I can 't see at night since my laser surgery .
What ?
Laser , to fix her vision .
- Are you better ? - Yes , thanks .
Yasmine , I forgot my glasses .
$ 0 ?
I can 't drive without them !
Are you serious ?
You can all spend the night here .
The house my brother built is empty .
You can stay in it .
No thanks , Saber . We should really get going .
Even tourists used to stay there .
Journalists too .
No , thank you .
Can you drive us to our car ?
We 'll get lost .
We really must get home , thanks .
Anyway , you 're welcome to stay .
I can always go check on the car .
We have to go . My grandfather will be worried sick .
Just drive us to the car .
Thank you .
Be right back . Think it over .
Thanks .
- Why so quiet ? - What about it ?
What about what ?
Sleeping here .
Are you nuts ?
I 'm going home . I won 't stay .
- Bashir must be freaking out . - Call him .
There 's no network ! No way !
Calm down , Yasmine .
We 'll leave at dawn .
I won 't wait till dawn . I 'm going home !
And drive in the dark ?
Why not ?
Aren 't I right ?
- No night vision , no glasses . - Good job !
You 'd rather have an accident ?
I won 't spend the night here .
Grandpa will worry .
Yasmine , listen to us .
No fucking way !
Come in .
Come in . Don 't be shy .
Welcome .
It 's been ages since we opened the house .
I can see that !
Make yourselves at home .
Yasmine , I asked the women . You can stay with them .
We prefer to stay together .
That would be inappropriate .
We 're like siblings .
Come on in , guys . Come in .
Thank you .
I 'll get some wood for the fireplace .
Thanks .
The Jacuzzi is there .
Very funny .
Creepy house !
It 's not a hotel . Shut up and go to sleep .
Only one bed .
Only one girl . Move !
That 's my spot .
Where do I sleep ?
Great .
Here .
Take it easy , asshole .
What is it ?
Stop being scared !
Is this some kind of joke ?
Thanks , Yasmine !
Walid , that 's my spot .
Shut up and sleep !
I don 't like this guy .
You , the first house .
You , the second door .
He saw us .
Good morning .
$ 0 ?
How was the night ?
Great ! What a palace !
The best we could offer .
You 're so kind , thanks . We slept well .
I wish I had more ...
How kind of you .
Saber ...
I want my charger from the car .
You 'll get lost alone . It 's a big forest .
I 'll take you when I drive the women .
You can 't go by foot .
Get ready .
Thanks a lot !
Bilel , here .
- Can 't you keep quiet ? - What did I say ?
You were rude to him .
I had an awful night 's sleep .
Why should I say it was great ?
Ever hear of common courtesy ?
I 'll learn it from you .
- Do ! - I 'm the one with back pain .
Poor thing .
It hurts like hell .
Shut up !
No need to be rude .
Leave me alone .
Don 't tell me to shut up .
And you had to film us sleeping ?
What the fuck ?
How do I rewind ?
- Damn , I deleted it ! - What 's wrong ?
- Nothing ! - Give me the camera !
What are you doing ?
Just watching the videos .
Never touch my camera !
Stick to sound .
Why so angry ?
Good morning .
Wait !
I 'm Yasmine .
We met at dinner .
What 's your name ?
You won 't say ?
Farah .
Nice to meet you .
How old are you ?
You don 't know ?
How long have you been pregnant ?
Seven months .
Great .
Why are you scared ?
What does a woman feel during pregnancy ?
Can you tell me ?
I 'm not pregnant .
Is it a boy or a girl ?
Run away . Now .
Damn you ! Go get the goats !
Why are you angry ?
What was she saying ?
We were talking about pregnancy .
She 's dumb !
I told you yesterday , women mustn 't speak to strangers .
She did nothing wrong !
Forget about her .
I asked the women to make couscous with meat .
- No ! - You have to .
We have to go home .
It will warm you up .
See you later .
- Did you film this morning ? - No .
We need footage .
We 'll get it .
Where 's Yasmine ?
Late .
Saber ! I 'm coming with you !
" M going back !
I hate him ! I 'm going to the car !
- Know the way ? - I 'll find it .
- Got the keys ? - Yes !
Stop it , please !
Why are you stressed ?
Stressed ? How so ?
I don 't know . Worried .
I 'm not .
So what is it ?
I spoke with the pregnant girl .
Which one ?
There 's only one pregnant girl .
And ?
I tried to film her .
She gave me the shivers .
How so ?
She was scared . She wouldn 't speak
or answer my questions .
She was terrified !
Then at one point ,
she came close and whispered :
" Run away ! Now ! "
Run away now ?
I swear !
- Are you sure ? - Totally !
So we must run away fast . My God ...
Are you teasing ? She really scared me !
Come on ! She 's a crazy girl !
Crazy ? Why are saying that ?
I can tell right away .
She 's jealous , so she said to go .
Jealous of what ?
Is the forest full of sexy boys ?
Cut it out !
So Saber is evil ?
You 're hopeless , I swear .
We have to go . Where is Bilel ?
Getting the charger .
I hope he 'll be back soon .
If a tiger killed him , I wouldn 't care .
Oh my God !
What is this ?
Hello , Walid .
Hi , Saber .
Madame Yasmine ...
It 's about the car ...
I checked on it .
- I 'm a bit ashamed . - Why ?
Some kids stole the tires .
What ?
How could they ?
Relax , it 's nothing .
- Seriously ? - No worries .
This is unacceptable .
- We towed it . - Towed ? What the hell ?
Don 't be scared . Everybody knows me around here .
Don 't make me mad !
The car was your responsibility .
They didn 't know you were my guests !
Shit ! How do we go home ?
What hospitality !
Don 't get mad . I 'll check on it again
and come back with good news .
I 'm sorry .
Happy now ? I said to go yesterday !
How will we get home ?
Is it me who stole the tires ?
I said to leave yesterday !
Yasmine !
Let 's go .
What 's going on ?
Let 's leave now !
- What happened ? - Now !
Take it easy !
Have Saber get the car .
There is no car .
- What ? - The tires were stolen .
No way !
It 's nothing . He 'll get it .
What 's wrong ?
- Blood ... - What ?
- Relax , it 's not real . - Slow down .
Tombs , blood , human bones !
There 's nothing . You 're paranoid .
Don 't push me !
Take it easy , you two .
Tell us what happened slowly .
He brought bags with bodies .
Bloody bags with bodies !
' - Sto t - ' p Crap !
- The bags ! - Follow him !
Saber !
Bilel !
A man in the woods gave you bags .
- I don 't get it ! - What 's inside ?
A slaughtered sheep for couscous !
I 'll get the car !
Are you satisfied ?
Happy now ?
What a wimp !
Are you out of your mind ?
Are you okay , Walid ?
Get up .
Are you insane ? What 's wrong with you ?
You 're crazy !
Walid !
Run away !
NOW !
September 12th , 1995 .
11 : 30 .
I reached the village , happy to find it by myself .
I got lost on the way ,
but then found it .
First thing I noticed ,
so many women .
I said hello but no one answered .
Hello .
The smell of firewood everywhere .
Meat hanging all over .
Maybe their customs ,
but it was weird .
Hello .
I kept saying hello , tried to speak ,
but no one answered .
The day I arrived ,
I met two men ,
silent as well .
I never saw them again .
My second day there .
I am kept in a cold house
but I had information to find .
I had a job to finish .
They made me a dinner of meat .
Weird taste .
Like nothing I ever ate .
The atmosphere here is heavy .
I am uncomfortable .
I want to leave .
I must finish this investigation .
And write the article I came to write .
Of the women here , only one intrigues me .
The woman in black .
Dressed in black ,
her face covered .
Everyone fears her .
- What you reading ? - Nothing .
Where 's Walid ?
I don 't know .
I 'm here .
Still mad ?
No .
Wait .
I 'll record some ambient noise .
- Sorry , my friend . - Forget it .
Don 't worry !
September 15 , 1995 .
Many women come to see the woman in black .
Most come at night .
My questions
went unanswered .
They seemed intrusive ,
but I must know what 's going on .
I want to know
what they 're doing with her .
I waited for nightfall .
I went .
I saw what I shouldn 't have .
Give her the picture .
Give her what she wants !
Witchcraft
is what these women practice .
That 's why they come to them .
Not only that .
What we suspected seems true .
Extracting treasures .
I thought the bags contained goats .
But the shouts are human . Children .
I found the hiding place .
It 's in the old hotel .
I don 't know where exactly .
They call them " zouhri " ,
holders of the key ,
a spot in the eye or a long line in the palm .
Silly beliefs , but they took many children .
Most of them beggars .
Orphans .
Some are kidnapped from hospitals .
Nobody believed my articles on the kidnappings .
I haven 't left the house for 3 days .
It 's raining hard .
Once in a while a woman knocks on my window
to see if I 'm still here .
But I can 't leave .
Something 's happening tonight .
I 'm sure of it .
Tonight ...
I 'm scared ...
I waited for the big woman to go .
Two women followed ,
then two men carrying bags .
I followed discreetly .
Don 't be afraid . I 'm here , don 't worry !
A girl of 3 or 4 was in the bag .
A red ribbon covered her face .
On her left hand , a birthmark .
A crescent moon ...
Bashir , take the girl . Take her !
Get in , quick !
I have to check something in the stable .
- I 'll call the cops ! - There are kids inside !
- I 'll call the cops . - Don 't !
Take care of her !
Tell her nothing till she grows up .
Don 't go . Come back !
My name is ...
Mongia ...
You ... you ...
The girl in the village ,
Rebeh ...
I took a picture of her ,
but I 've seen her before .
I 'm not crazy . I 've seen her before .
In old pictures .
When the hotel was still open .
In 1920 .
She 's still the same .
She hasn 't grown up .
Yasmine !
Look .
What 's that ?
She 's giving birth ?
They deliver babies with knives ?
Is it the baby ?
Something weird is going on .
Where is she taking him ?
Follow her .
I 'm not budging .
Then I 'll do it .
If you won 't , I will .
- Let 's go home . - What 's wrong ?
- Let 's leave . - What is it ?
- They 'll kill us ! - Who ?
- They 'll kill us ! - Yasmine , calm down !
- Let 's leave . - Once we get the car .
There is no car ! Don 't open !
- Maybe it 's Walid . - It 's not !
" I seek refuge with the Lord of Mankind ,
" the King of Mankind , the God of Mankind .
" From the mischief of the Whisperer ,
" who withdraws and whispers
" into the hearts of Mankind ,
" among genies and men . "
Get up , my child .
I 'm here now . Don 't be scared .
Hold onto me and walk .
Hurry UP -
He 's dead , Yasmine .
God have mercy on him .
Walk faster .
Yasmine !
It 's Walid .
Get up , Walid , please get up .
Have her release the " Thing " .
Yasmine , get up and run away .
No ...
We 'll follow you . Come on , run !
Something weird happened .
I 'll get the permit .
M0ngia !
You forgot the map .
That 's the spot .
Her name is Algia ?
No , Mongia .
Eat . It 's tasty .
Yasmine , I forgot my glasses .
Let 's sleep here .
She 's the one .